https://www.billmax.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to www.billmax.com and The iSpark Group and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to The iSpark Group include www.billmax.com and BillMax Billing Solutions. The BillMax Billing Solutions website is a Sales and information site. By using the BillMax Billing Solutions website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
In order to better provide you with products and services offered on our Site, BillMax Billing Solutions may collect personally identifiable information, such as your:
– First and Last Name– E-mail Address– Phone Number
We do not collect any personal information about you unless you voluntarily provide it to us. However, you may be required to provide certain personal information to us when you elect to use certain products or services available on the Site. These may include: (a) registering for an account on our Site; (b) entering a sweepstakes or contest sponsored by us or one of our partners; (c) signing up for special offers from selected third parties; (d) sending us an email message; (e) submitting your credit card or other payment information when ordering and purchasing products and services on our Site. To wit, we will use your information for, but not limited to, communicating with you in relation to services and/or products you have requested from us. We also may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.
Use of your Personal Information
BillMax Billing Solutions collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.
BillMax Billing Solutions may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from BillMax Billing Solutions and its affiliates.
Sharing Information with Third Parties
BillMax Billing Solutions does not sell, rent or lease it’s customer lists to third parties.
BillMax Billing Solutions may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to BillMax Billing Solutions, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
BillMax Billing Solutions may disclose your personal information, without notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on BillMax Billing Solutions or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of BillMax Billing Solutions; and/or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of BillMax Billing Solutions, or the public.
Tracking User Behavior
BillMax Billing Solutions may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within BillMax Billing Solutions, in order to determine what BillMax Billing Solutions services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within BillMax Billing Solutions to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
Automatically Collected Information
Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by BillMax Billing Solutions. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the BillMax Billing Solutions website.
Links
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
Children Under Thirteen
BillMax Billing Solutions does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.
E-mail Communications
From time to time, BillMax Billing Solutions may contact you via email for the purpose of providing announcements, promotional offers, alerts, confirmations, surveys, and/or other general communication.
If you would like to stop receiving marketing or promotional communications via email from BillMax Billing Solutions, you may opt out of such communications by clicking on the UNSUBSCRIBE button or emailing sales@billmax.com.
Changes to this Statement
BillMax Billing Solutions reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account, by placing a prominent notice on our site, and/or by updating any privacy information on this page. Your continued use of the Site and/or Services available through this Site after such modifications will constitute your: (a) acknowledgment of the modified Privacy Policy; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by that Policy.
Contact Information
BillMax Billing Solutions welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that BillMax Billing Solutions has not adhered to this Statement, please contact BillMax Billing Solutions at:
Email Address: sales@billmax.com
Telephone number: 817-446-7776
Effective as of March 08, 2019
About Us
The BillMax Way
News/Events
Alerts
Contact Us
Partners
Request Demo
We use technical and analytics cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. Please accept the use of cookies.I AcceptPrivacy policy
